蒂芬妮:蒂芬妮齐恩现在苏福县法院向您报道.今天,
Tiffany: Tiffany Ching here at the Sufa county court house where the trial
奥利弗马丁一案继续审理.
of Oliver Martin continues today.
马丁这位着名的赛马骑手在法庭宣誓.
Martin the noted Jockey was sworn in then testified that he indeed throw
他作证说确实伤着了布里斯奇汉迪凯,
the briskee handy ca,
但这都是他的那匹叫"瘦骨嶙峋"的马让他这么做的.
but only because his horse "Bone Weary" told him to do it.
被告的目击证人,
The defense's star witness, psychiatrist, Jason Weaver,
着名的心理学家杰森西沃作证说马丁确实精神失常.作完证后,
testified that Martin was indeed insane.After his testimony, Dr.
西沃医生发表了评论.
Seaver offered this comment.
记者:西沃医生!!!
Reporters: Dr.Seaver!!!
杰森:无可奉告,无可奉告!
Jason: No comment, no comment!
麦琪:不要!不要!不要!
Maggie: Don't!Don't!Don't!
克莉丝:我可以让爸爸像只鸭子一样倒着走.
Chrissy: I can make daddy walk backwards like a duck.
开萝尔:克莉丝,这不是玩具,是大人用的.
Carol: Chrissy, it's not a toy, it's for grown ups.
迈克:对,就这样.我还可以让他跳恰恰.
Mike: Yeah right, and besides I can make him Cha-cha.
本:在来一次!我还想看.
Ben: Do it again!I want to see it.
迈克:好,好,好好看着.
Mike: Ok, ok. Alright watch this.
本:哈!
Ben: Ha!
迈克:很好玩,是吧?
Mike: Pretty good huh?
麦琪:哦,可怜的孩子.我都等不及了,你的眼镜快点送来啊.
Maggie: Oh, my poor baby, I can't wait till those glasses of yours come in.
卢克:它们还在医生那里.实际上,
Luke: They're in the doctor called yesterday.Actually it was another doctor...
是另外一个医生…是胡椒医生.
Dr.Pepper.
杰森:大家好!
Jason: Hello everybody!
麦琪:好,亲爱的.
Maggie: Hi honey.
克莉丝:爸爸!你上电视了!
Chrissy: Daddy!You were on TV!
杰森:对啊.
Jason: Yeah.
麦琪:哦,杰森!我们都以你为荣!
Maggie: Oh Jason!We're all so proud of you!
杰森:准备好了,还有更光荣的呢.
Jason: Well get ready to be even more proud.
猜猜因为公开审理这个案子,
Guess what I was offered because of all this trial publicity?
我获得了什么?为写专栏文章.
A column in the Long Island Sentinel.
克莉丝:太棒了,爸爸!!什么是专栏?
Chrissy: That's great daddy!!What's a column?
麦琪:哦,专栏就是你写的一种…哦,
Maggie: Well it's something you write that...
宝贝,
Well sweetheart it's something that is hard to explain if you haven't
如果你没读过报纸,这很难向你解释专栏是什么
read a newspaper.
本:但我们还是想知道.
Ben: But some of us would still like to know.
麦琪:就是…
Maagie: Well it's....
杰森:本,就是围绕一个主题撰写的一些列文章.
Jason: Ben, it's a series of articles all on one theme,
我的专栏是关于心理学的.
mine will deal with psychology.
我要帮助人们克服恐惧,增加希望,
I'll help people with their fears,
解析梦境和幻想.
and their hopes and their dreams and their fantasies.
本:这就像900号码.
Ben: Kind of like a 900 number.
克莉丝:什么是900号码?
Chrissy: What's a 900 number?
本:哦,这是一种很昂贵但…呃…我不知道.
Ben: Well it's kind of expensive but....uhhh...I have no idea.
我是说我从不一分钟付两美元去跟穿比基尼的姑娘聊天.
I mean I've never paid 2 dollars a minute to talk to some girl in a bikini.
嘿,我们去做热苹果派吧.
Hey kids let's go bake a hot apple pie.
开萝尔:我说你的专栏听起来很棒,爸爸.
Carol: Well I think your column sounds great dad.
糟糕的是,你的孩子们太幼稚无法欣赏它.
It's just too bad your children aren't mature enough to appreciate it.
本,你这呆子!!你把我的录像洗掉了.
Ben you moron!!You taped over Bambi!
麦琪:杰森,多说说你的专栏吧.
Maggie: Jason tell me more about you column.
杰森:我已经在电话里和编辑说好了.
Jason: Well I worked it all out over the phone with the editor,
那个人叫道格司坦顿.
a guy named Doug Stanton.
麦琪:道格?是那个一分钱掰两半花的那个司坦顿?
Maggie: Doug if you give the penny, I'll pinch it Stanton?
杰森:我没记住他的全名.
Jason: Well Pinch is his middle name.
麦琪:哦,几年前,
Maggie: Oh I worked for him years ago.
我给他干过.付作者稿费的时候,他会斤斤计较的.
When it comes to paying writers he can be frugal.
杰森:对待金钱,
Jason: You got to get up pretty early in the morning to frugal Jason Seaver,
杰森肺魑忠膊皇鞘∮偷牡疲箸鳌6遥沂歉鎏旨刍辜鄣母呤帧?
Maggie.And something else, I'm a good negotiator.
麦琪:哦,好.稿费是多少?
Maggie: Oh good, what's he paying?
杰森:哦,我们还没搞定这个呢?
Jason: Well we haven't nailed that down yet.
麦琪:你的专栏要写多长?
Maggie: How long is the column suppose to be?
杰森:有时长,有时短,这只是…
Jason: Sometimes long, sometimes short.It just...
麦琪:每天一篇?每周一篇?
Maggie: Daily?Weekly?
杰森:还没定呢.
Jason: It's unstructured still .
麦琪:那一定有你的署名了.
Maggie: Well I assume your getting Bylines.
杰森:麦琪,都还没确定呢.
Jason: Maggie, not all this is etched in stone.
麦琪:换句话说就是谈判家先生,
Maggie: So in other words Mr.
你辛苦写作也许得不到几个钱或根本没有报酬,
Negotiator, you could be working long hours for little or no money while
而别人却坐享其成.
someone else gets the credit.
杰森:我被骗了.
Jason: I've been frugaled.
麦琪:道格司坦顿,你又在干什么坏事呢?
Maggie: Doug Stanton you conniving piece of filth.
道格:麦琪马龙,你这个离开我去加盟的坏家伙.
Doug: Maggie Malone, the bubblehead that left me for the five o'clock news.
麦琪:我多年都不上电视了.忘了吧.
Maggie: I haven't been on TV for ages, get over it.
道格:我不说了.坐下!跟我谈谈!我这可没有电视播放提示板.
Doug: I won't say another word.Sit!Talk to me!That is if you can handle it without a teleprompt.
哪阵风把你给吹来了?你想实地考察人们是怎么工作谋生的吗?
So what brings you here?You want to actually see people work for a living?
麦琪:我丈夫是杰森西沃.
Maggie: My husband is Jason Seaver.
道格:那个奥利弗马丁惹的案子!?那个精神病医生!!?我雇了他给我们写专栏呢.
Doug: What the Oliver Martin case!?The shrink with the big hair!!?I hired him to do a column for us.
麦琪:我来这是为了告诉你千万别利用他.
Maggie: I'm here to make sure you don't take advantage of him.
道格:麦琪!你侮辱我呢!!我给他两倍的基本稿酬外加最高的补贴.
Doug: Maggie!I'm insulted!!I'm giving him double basic with inflated top end.
麦琪:真的??那你给那些文字记者多少?
Maggie: Really??And how much do you pay the paper boys?
道格:没有最高的补贴.
Doug: Well no top end.
麦琪:除了体面的薪水外,
Maggie: Just after a decent salary and some guarantees on column length
还要保证专栏的长度和署名.
and bylines
道格:麦琪!你太为难我了!
Doug: Maggie!You're killing me!
麦琪:你想不想要他?
Maggie: Do you want him or not?
道格:好吧,我给他高规格的酬劳.
Doug: Ok, I'll pay him senior scale,
但你千万别跟文字记者们透漏半个字.
but don't you dare say a word about this to the paper boys.
麦琪:成交.
Maggie: Done.
道格:我要砸烂这个废物机器.
Doug: I am going to smash this worthless piece of junk.
麦琪:你买了2000型??
Maggie: You bought the Shitake 2000??
你为什么不学会使用呢??
Why don't you just paint ink on your hands??
把这个按下去,我把这个塞进去.
Here hold this down while I feed this through the J clips.
道格:你什么时候学会摆弄打印机了?
Doug: When did you learn so much about printers?
麦琪:我研究过.每当买了大件物品,
Maggie: I research them, when I make a major purchase I do my homework.
我都认真做研究.弄好了.
There all better.
道格:等等,这可以写个专栏.每周,你可以告诉读者们如何花最少的钱买称心的东西.
Doug: Now wait a minute, this could be a column.Every week you could tell
my readers how to get the best value for their dollar
麦琪:我来找你是谈杰森的专栏的.
Maggie: Well I came here to talk about Jason's column.
道格:我知道..我们有足够的版面供你们俩写.
Doug: Well sure, there's enough room for both of you.
他可以写精神方面的,你可以写微波炉,
He'll do the shrink stuff, you do the microwaves, VCR's, furniture polish,
录像机和家具上光等消费方面的.
all that Ralph Nader crud.
麦琪:你是说消费顾问吗?
Maggie: You mean consumer awareness?
道格:怎么样??你对这个很在行.
Doug: See??You got a handle on this already.
麦琪,干吧,
Maggie come on, your writing is punchy, to the point,
你的文笔犀利,主题鲜明,我知道你从不用被动句或专业术语这样晦涩的词.
I know you'll never use a passive sentence or a fancy buzzword like buzzword.
你觉得怎么样?
What do you say?
麦琪:我的薪水能有多少?
Maggie: Will I receive some form of salary?
道格:麦琪,你又为难我了!!
Doug: Maggie, You're killing me!!
克莉丝:你在干什么呢,迈克?
Chrissy: What are you doing Mike?
迈克:哦,我在准备下周的教学计划呢.
Mike: Well, I'm making out my lesson plan for next week.
开萝尔:哦,你要不要借克莉丝的蜡笔呢?
Carol: Oh would you like to borrow, Chrissy's crayons?
杰森:女士们,先生们,塔-达!
Jason: Ladies and Gentlemen, Tada!
本:再来一下,我就走了.
Ben: One crack and I'm gone.
杰森:迈克,不许笑!
Jason: Mike, cut that out!
迈克:你不知道在说什么,爸爸.
Mike: You don't know what you're asking dad.
开萝尔:我说说,我觉得你看起来很有学问.
Carol: Well I'll say something, I think you look brainy.
本:啊!
Ben: Ah!!
迈克:哦!!别拦着他,爸爸,我肺都快气炸了.
Mike: OH!!Don't stop him dad, my pancreas is about to blow.
本:爸爸,有学问就等同于滑稽小丑.
Ben: Dad, brainy is just another word for geek.
杰森:我戴着眼睛呢,我不是小丑.
Jason: I wear glasses, I'm not a geek.
本:就是,你都结婚了.
Ben: Sure, you've got a woman.
迈克:哦,天啊.我得躺下了,我也许笑岔气了.
Mike Oh god, I got to go lay down.I think I just hurt myself.
麦琪:嘿,大家好.
Maggie: Hi everybody.
杰森:嘿.
Jason: Hey.
麦琪:猜猜结果如何!?
Maggie: Guess what!?
杰森:你跟道格司坦顿谈的很顺利!?
Jason: Your meeting went well with Doug Stanton!?
麦琪:哦,还用说吗?我是为你去的.听好了,
Maggie: Oh did it ever?And I got you, hold on to your hat.
我帮你争取到比文字记者还多的薪水.再猜猜我得到了什么?
I got you more money than the paper boys.And guess what I was offered?
杰森:三大口袋薄饼烤模.
Jason: Three bags full of waffle irons.
麦琪:不,是一个专栏.
Maggie: No, a column.
杰森:亲爱的,你也写专栏!!?太棒了!
Jason: Honey, you're writing a column too!!?That's wonderful!
开萝尔:担子不轻啊,妈妈!
Carol: Way to go mom!
麦琪:专栏的名字就叫.
Maggie: I'm going to call it,
我要用这些东西来做第一篇文章的素材.
Maggie Malone consumer watchdog and I'm testing these for my first piece.
周末我们就吃薄饼.
So its waffles all weekend.
克莉丝:好啊!!!
Chrissy: Yes!!!
麦琪:别动,我去接.
Maggie: Hold on, I'll get it.
开萝尔:一家出了两个专栏作家,这太棒了.
Carol: Isn't this exciting two people in the same family with columns.
克莉丝:爸爸,妈妈拿薄饼写专栏,你拿什么呢???
Chrissy: Daddy.Mommy gets waffles with her column, what do you get!???
杰森:我不写物质方面的,
Jason: Well it's not a material thing,
我的主题是帮助别人解决难题而获得的满足感.
just the satisfaction I get out of helping people solve their problems.
克莉丝:哦,这很…枯燥啊.
Chrissy: Oh that's nice.Boring.
麦琪:我也很遗憾.谢谢.
Maggie: Well I'm sorry too.Thank you.
好的,我就知道太好的事不保险.
Well, I knew it was too good to be true.
杰森:谁打来的?
Jason: Who was that?
麦琪:道格司坦顿.报社社长削减了他的预算,
Maggie: Doug Stanton, his publisher slashed his budget so he only has
他手里的钱只够一个专栏的了.
enough money for one column.
杰森:他最好别砍你的专栏…他最好别砍我的专栏.
Jason: Well he better not cut your column...He better not cut my column.
那谁被砍掉了?
Who got the axe here?
麦琪:谁也没.他居然想出一个主意,让我们各自试写一篇专栏看谁能留下.
Maggie: Neither, you know he actually had the never to for each of us to submit a sample column.
我说我们不搞竞争.
I told him we refuse to compete.
杰森:你是怎么说的?
Jason: Are you saying?
麦琪:我说专栏由你来写.
Maggie: I'm saying the column is all yours.
杰森:这太惭愧了!我很遗憾,麦琪.你想的开吗?
Jason: That's one darn shame!I'm sorry Maggie.Are you alright with that?
麦琪:这有什么.开萝尔,
Maggie: I'm fine, Carol, Chrissy,
克莉丝,帮我把这些该死的薄饼烤模装进口袋里.
please help me pack these stupid waffle irons.
杰森:你说什么该死的,这表明你有情绪.我能感受到.
Jason: You said stupid and that is a sign of tension.I'm sensing it.
麦琪:别犯傻了.我很开心,因为你,杰森.
Maggie: Don't be silly, I'm very happy for you Jason.
杰森:真的?
Jason: You sure?
麦琪:千真万确.
Maggie: Absolutely.
杰森:很好.不,不是.开萝尔,
Jason: Good.No no no, Carol, Chrissy, stop packing.
克莉丝,别装了.麦琪,
Maggie, I am a professional at this and I'm sensing your pain here and
我是这方面的专家,我感觉到你的痛苦.如果我让你放弃专栏的话,你永远不会原谅我的.
if I let you give up your column you would never forgive me.
麦琪:你是说你要放弃你的专栏!?
Maggie: So you are saying you will give up your column!?
杰森:那我永远不会原谅你.
Jason: Just as I would never forgive you.
我们还是让司坦顿来决定吧.
I think we ought to let Stanton decide.
麦琪:杰森,我们俩相互竞争可不是个好主意.
Maggie: Jason, I don't think it's a good idea our competing.
杰森:哦,我们别想成是竞争,
Jason: Well, let's not think of this as competing Maggie.
麦琪.我们把它看作是一次开创美好事业的机会就好了.
Let's see it as a chance for both of us to have something wonderful.
麦琪:哦,真这样吗!!?我给大家做薄饼.
Maggie: Oh what the heck!!?Desert waffles for everybody.
克莉丝:好啊!!
Chrissy: Yes!!
本:有人说薄饼?
Ben: Somebody said waffles?
麦琪:哦,本!我喜欢你的眼镜.你看起来很有学问.
Maggie: Oh Ben!I love your glasses, They make you look so brainy.
本:这下好了,我还是去死吧.
Ben: That settles it, I'm gonna die a virgin.
开萝尔:这是我的家吗?迈克西沃竟然一天用功了两次?
Carol: Am I in the right house?Mike Seaver studying twice in a same day?
迈克:算了吧!别笑话我了,
Mike: Come on!Let's get it down, Carol.
开萝尔,我只是在研究技术性很强,很复杂的问题罢了.
I'm working on something very technical and complex here.
麦琪:迈克.你填完薄饼问卷了吗?
Maggie: Mike, have you finished the waffle questionnaire yet?
迈克:是的.
Mike: Yeah.
杰森:我给自己的专栏起了个好名字-
Jason: I've got a great title for my column.
Between your ears with Jason Seaver?
麦琪:听起来罗里罗嗦的.简洁点吧,叫怎么样?
Maggie: Sounds kind of crowded.How about something punchy like Shrink wrap?
杰森:不,严肃点.你喜欢我起的名字吗?
Jason: No no, seriously, how do you like mine?
麦琪:哈哈哈.克莉丝,快点,该上床睡觉了.
Maggie: Ha ha ha, Chrissy come on, it's time for you to go to bed.
开萝尔:老天,妈妈和爸爸在大动干戈呢.
Carol: Boy, Mom and Dad are flirting with big trouble.
迈克:你在说什么呢,开萝尔?
Mike: What are you talking about Carol?
开萝尔:妈妈和爸爸俩在争同一个专栏!
Carol: Mom and Dad both going after the same column!!?
竞争可是爱情花园里的杂草.
Competition is a weed in the garden of love.
迈克:而你开萝尔就是肥料了?哦,
Mike: And you Carol are the fertilizer?Oh come on!
得了吧!为什么你总是大惊小怪的.
Why are you making such a big deal out of this for?
开萝尔:因为这是件大事.我怎么给你解释清楚呢?打个比方吧.
Carol: Because it is a big deal.How can I explain it to you?Let me use an example.
迈克:那好啊.
Mike: Ok fine.
开萝尔:假设我和你互相在争一件东西,好吗?于是,我和你,兄妹两人.
Carol:  Suppose you and I were competing against each other for something ok?So there we are brother and sister.
迈克:我们争什么?
Mike: What are we competing at?
开萝尔:无关紧要.只是个例子.好吗?于是我们两个…
Carol: It doesn't matter, it's an example.Ok?So there we are.
迈克:那我怎么懂你的例子啊,
Mike: Now, how can I follow your example,
如果你不说我们竞争什么?
if I don't know what we are competing at?
开萝尔:那好吧,就背单词吧.
Carol: Ok fine, it's a spelling bee.
迈克:好,就它了.
Mike: Ok fine.
开萝尔:好.我们两个…
Carol: Good.So there we are.
迈克:等一下,为什么要背单词呢?
Mike: Wait a minute, why would I want to be in a spelling bee?
开萝尔:无所谓的,只是个假设罢了.
Carol: It doesn't matter, it's a hypothetical situation.
迈克:但我会一败涂地的.我们还是来点我擅长的,好吗?
Mike: But Carol you would beat the pants off me, now can't we just pick something I'm good at?
开萝尔:好的,就来一对一打篮球怎么样?
Carol: Ok fine, how about one on one basketball?
迈克:好.
Mike: Ok.
开萝尔:那好,打篮球,于是我们两个…
Carol: Great.Basketball, so there we are.
迈克:你为什么要跟我打篮球呢?你连运球都不会.
Mike: Why would you want to play basketball against me?You can't even dribble.
开萝尔:啊!
Carol: Ah!
杰森:迈克,开萝尔,
Jason: Mike, Carol.How does this sound for my first piece?
听听我的第一篇专栏水平任何?本我,自我以及超我把自己融入到一个没有兄弟友爱的世界里.
The id, ego and superego, merging the self in a non fraternal world.
迈克:哦,我喜欢,爸爸.太棒了.
Mike: Ooh, I like that dad.That's great.
杰森:我也是.我喜欢,我兴奋.
Jason: I think so, I like it.I'm excited.
开萝尔:开玩笑呢,你懂吗?
Carol: You're kidding, you understood that?
迈克:是的,爸爸写的是有关兄弟友爱的文章.
Mike: Yeah, dad's writing an article about fraternities.
麦琪:杰森,这是被动句吗?
Maggie: Jason, is that a passive sentence?
杰森:哪一句?
Jason: Which one?
麦琪:这句,还有这句,以及包含这个模糊术语的这句.
Maggie: That one.And that one, and this one with the word buzzword in it.
杰森:很好,对吗?
Jason: Pretty good huh?
麦琪:有意思的是竟然有人不喜欢这个词.实际上,
Maggie: It's funny how some people don't like that word.
一些人谈眼这个词.杰森,删掉它吧.
As a matter of fact some people hate that word.Jason, lose the word.
杰森:亲爱的,我并不是第一次写这样的文章.
Jason: Honey, it's not like this is the first time I've ever been published.
麦琪:是的,那是给其他精神病专家看的,这次是普通读者.
Maggie: Yes, that was for other psychiatrists, this is for actual people.
杰森:那我使用流行点的术语怎么样,亲爱的?
Jason: Why do you think I used the popular term buzzword darling??
麦琪:直话直说,
Maggie: Cupcake, I'm just trying to give you the benefit of 20 years of
我真想把20年记者的经验和本事都传授给你.
journalistic experience.
杰森:我很感谢你的无私和表现出来的爱意.但我还是要继续写已经证实了的科学理论,
Jason: And I appreciate that puppy toes and all the love it shows,
but I'm going to continue to write about my proven scientific theory while
you can confine
你可以继续写你自己拿手的,恕我直言,薄饼.
yourself to writing about, I'm just going to say it.Waffles.
麦琪:我还是明天再写吧.
Maggie: Maybe I'll work on this tomorrow.
杰森:我也是.我有点累了.
Jason: Me too.I'm kind of tired.
杰森:你打开窗户了?
Jason: You're opening the window?
麦琪:我觉得有点闷.
Maggie: It's a little stuffy in here.
杰森:很好,你想干什么就干什么吧.
Jason: Fine, have the house you want it Maggie.
别担心我的硬脖子.
Don't worry about my stuff neck.
麦琪:我不知道,你脖子不舒服?
Maggie: I didn't know you had a stiff neck?
杰森:哦,不,
Jason: Oh no, I didn't mention it,
我没说.因为我不想你的脖子也硬起来.
because I was afraid you would want one too.
麦琪:你说这话是什么意思啊?
Maggie: Now what is that suppose to mean?
杰森:哦,没什么,麦琪,随便说说罢了.
Jason: Oh nothing Maggie, just a little shrink wrap.
窗户由我来关,是的,这是一个被动句,
The window will now be closed by me which yes I realize is a passive sentence
麦琪,但一样可以关上.该死.
Maggie, but it does get the job done.Stupid.
麦琪:让我来关吗?
Maggie: Want me to do it?
杰森:哦,什么都是权威,是的.
Jason: Oh the authority on everything, yes.
麦琪:事实上,我就是.
Maggie: As a matter of fact, I am.
杰森:你不应该关上窗户的,麦琪,现在你会不舒服的.
Jason: You shouldn't have closed the widow Maggie, now you will be uncomfortable.
麦琪:不,杰森,
Maggie: No Jason, because I will be much more comfortable sleeping on
因为我睡在冰冷的地板上也比睡在你身边舒服的多.
the cold hard floor than next to you.
杰森:哦,你太体贴了,
Jason: Oh that's real mature Maggie.
麦琪.那我就睡在温暖舒适的床上,你睡在地上好吗?
How am I going to sleep in this nice warm bed when you're down there?
麦琪:这张温暖舒适的床是你铺的,你就睡那里吧.
Maggie: You made your nice warm bed now lie in it.
杰森:我不睡,你不能指使我.
Jason: I won't and you can't make me.
麦琪:我不相信你怎么会这样.
Maggie: I can't believe you're doing this.
杰森:我就这样,麦琪,我全是一个人这么过来的.我干的就是比你强.
Jason: I'm doing it Maggie and I'm doing it all by myself and I'm doing it better than you.
麦琪:好!
Maggie: Fine!
杰森:好.
Jason: Fine.
麦琪:晚安!
Maggie: Goodnight!
杰森:晚安.
Jason: Goodnight.
迈克:各位,我们已经吃了比利时薄饼,
Mike: Guys we have had Belgian waffles, Mystique waffles, Mushu waffles,
密制薄饼,玉米糊薄饼,兰彻罗薄饼.
Waffles Rancheros.
有谁知道今晚吃什么?
Does anyone know what the heck that was last night?
克莉丝:洋葱猪肝薄饼.啊!!
Chrissy: Liver onion waffles.Ughh!!
开萝尔:别闹了,你们.
Carol: Knock it off you guys,
妈妈写不完她的专栏,我们还要继续吃下去的.
we have to keep eating these waffles until mom finishes her column.
麦琪:哦,昨晚我就写完了,亲爱的.
Maggie: Oh, I finished my column last night honey.
开萝尔:那你为什么还让我们吃这些该死的薄饼??
Carol: Then why are you ramming these stinking waffles down our throats!!??
本:薄饼!?
Ben: Waffles!?
卢克:是的!太好了!
Luke: Yes!Excellent!
开萝尔:我去拿麦片.
Carol: I'll get the cereal.
本:啊!开萝尔把我的眼镜压折了!
Ben: Ahh!Carol broke my glasses!
开萝尔:你放到我的椅子上干什么?
Carol: Well, what were they doing on my chair!!??
本:这不重要,重要的是眼镜折了.
Ben: That's not important, the important thing is they're broken.
麦琪:是真的吗??
Maggie: Are you sure??
本:是的!眼镜折了!
Ben: Yes!They're broken!
迈克:不,没有,你这个小四眼,只是给压弯了.
Mike: No they're not you nearsighted little weeny.They're just bent.
本:是折了!
Ben: They're broken!
麦琪:好了,宝贝,如果你的眼镜折了,一小条胶带就能让它恢复如初的.
Maggie: Well sweetheart if your glasses are broken, a little masking tape will make them as good as new.
本:胶带!?呃…我看错了,它没折.太神奇了!我看的见!我看的见!
Ben: Masking tape!?Uhh... I was wrong, they're not broken, It's a miracle!I can see!I can see!
杰森:早上好,各位.
Jason: Good morning family.
迈克:嘿,爸爸.
Mike: Hey dad.
杰森:你是最可爱的.
Jason: Dearest.
麦琪:亲爱的,今天上午我就把专栏文章交到道格的办公室.
Maggie: My love.I will be taking my column back to Doug's office this
我很乐意把你的一块交上去.
morning, It'll be my pleasure to bring yours with me.
杰森:哦,你想的太周到了.
Jason: Oh how very thoughtful of you?But then you always are.
你总是这样的.哦,我来帮你.
Oh let me help you with that.
麦琪:哦,谢谢你杰森.你真是体贴.
Maggie: Oh thank you Jason, how very thoughtful of you.
杰森:微薄之力而已.慢点走.我来.
Jason: The least I could do.Watch your step.I'll get that.
麦琪:谢谢.
Maggie: Thank you.
杰森:客气.
Jason: Ok.
开萝尔:老天啊!!他们俩人要展开生死搏斗了.
Carol: My gosh!!Those two are ready to go for each other's throats.
迈克:哦,开萝尔,你就像一张坏唱片那样讨厌.他们是恩爱的一对.
Mike: Oh Carol, you sound like a broken record.They're just being lovey dovey.
本:是的,开萝尔,他们看起来很开心,因为他们本来就很开心.
Ben: Yeah Carol, newsflash maybe they're acting happy cause they're happy.
卢克:是的.整个周末他们没说过一句气话.
Luke: Yeah, has anyone heard an angry word out of them all weekend?
克莉丝:如果他们闹别扭,是逃不过我们的眼睛的.
Chrissy: If they were really mad they could never hide it from us.
麦琪:道格要在3点钟约见我们,你方便吗?
Maggie: Doug would like to see us at 3 o'clock is that ok for you?
杰森:方便,回头见.
Jason: Perfect, see you then.
开萝尔:你们看!现在明白我说的话了吧!?
Carol: There!Now do you see what I'm talking about!?
迈克:你是预言家?
Mike: Judges?
卢克,本,迈克,克莉丝:哼!!
Luke, Ben, Mike, Chrissy: Een!!
本:哦,肯尼,第一天当小丑宣告结束了.
Ben: Well Kenny, my first day of geekdom is officially over.
肯尼:本,很多酷哥也戴眼镜的.
Kenny: Ben, cool guys wear glasses too you know.
本:是吗!??说出20个来.
Ben: Yeah!??Name 20.
肯尼:伍笛艾伦,海斯福里希亚诺,埃科…
Kenny: Woody Allen, Hays Forli Ciano, Aco...
本:埃科?
Ben: Aco?
肯尼:我妹妹喜欢他们.
Kenny: My sister likes them.
本:她才4岁.
Ben: She's 4 years old.
肯尼:那克拉克肯特怎么样?他戴眼镜就赢得了罗伊斯莱恩的欢心.
Kenny: What abut Clark Kent?He wears glasses and he has Lois Lane.
本:克拉克肯特戴眼镜的时候,罗伊斯根本不搭理他.
Ben: When he's Clark Kent he doesn't give him the time of the day,
但一摘下眼镜,他们马上就好上了.
but as soon as though glasses come off, ba bing ba boom.
快看,那是杰希卡哈特.
Look over there it's Jessica Hart,
从5年级我就喜欢她,但她根本不知道我这个人.
I've had a crush on her since the fifth grade,
屏住气,她过来了.
she doesn't even know I'm alive.Don't breathe here she comes.
杰希卡:嘿,你是不是上过第三期的英语课啊?
Jessica: Hi, aren't you in my third period English class?
呃…
Ben: Uhh...
杰希卡:我认出你的帅眼镜了.你是新生吗?
Jessica: I recognize those cool glasses, are you new in school?
本:是的.
Ben: Yes.
杰希卡:我叫杰希卡,你呢?
Jessica: My name is Jessica, what's yours?
本:克拉克肯特.
Ben: Kent, Clark Kent.
杰希卡:你愿意陪我去车站吗,克拉克?
Jessica: You want to walk me to the bus Clark?
本:当然.大功告成.
Ben: Sure.Ba bing ba boom.
麦琪:道格,你这条隐藏在草丛里的毒蛇.
Maggie: Doug, you slimy snake in the grass.
道格:你是个没脑子的笨狗.
Doug: You walking Cupee Dog.
杰森:司坦顿,你这只老蛤蟆.
Jason: Stanton you old Toad.
道格:嘿,够了,你伤着我了.
Doug: Hey, take it easy I got feelings.
杰森:对不起.
Jason: Sorry.
道格:坐下.麦琪马龙,杰森西沃.我们谈谈吧!
Doug: Sit.Maggie Malone, Jason Seaver.Talk to me!
麦琪:你叫他老蛤蟆!??
Maggie: You old toad!??
杰森:多像啊.
Jason: I drew a blank.
道格:你站着别动.
Doug: No you stay where you are.
我要那裁纸刀过去把你的心挖出来用脚踩.我喜欢这么做.
I'm coming down there with a letter opener to cut out your heart and stomp
等一下.
on it.I love this business.One minute.
杰森:我想,我们这么看他们是不对的.
Jason: I guess it would be wrong for us to look at them.
麦琪:是的,很不专业.
Maggie: Yes., very unprofessional.
杰森:哦!!我的文章没有一处批注!
Jason: Whoa!!Mine doesn't have a mark on it!
麦琪:可我的上面全是红墨水.
Maggie: Mine does, it's covered in red ink.
杰森:这并不意味着他不喜欢.
Jason: Well that doesn't necessarily mean he doesn't like it.
麦琪:杰森,他耍了个花招.
Maggie: Jason, he used it as a coaster.
我想是不是该向你表示祝贺了?
I suppose a congratulations are in order?
杰森:亲爱的,相信我,当我鼓励你坚持下去的时候,我从没奢望,
Jason: Honey, believe me when I encouraged you to follow this thing through
哦,我奢望过,但我真的不想…
I never dreamed, well I dreamed, but I really didn't think...
麦琪:杰森,我替你感到高兴.
Maggie: Jason I'm very happy for you.
杰森:我知道的.我会补偿你的.
Jason: I know you are.I'll make it up to you.
道格:好了,刚才说到哪了?哦,对.我太太说我对人太粗暴了.我正努力改正呢.杰森,我喜欢你的领带.
Doug: Ok, well where were we?Oh right.My wife tells me I'm too blunt
with people.I'm trying to work on it.Jason, I love your tie
杰森:哦,谢谢.
Jason: Oh thank you.
道格:看了你的专栏,我真想呕吐.
Doug: Your column wanted to make me toss my cookies.
麦琪做几处改动,我们可以发表在晨报上面.
Maggie make a few changes, we can get that in the morning edition.
麦琪:你把专栏给我了吗?
Maggie: You're giving me the column?
道格:当然了,你以为什么?
Doug: Of course what did you think?
麦琪:我还以为…
Maggie: Well I thought...
杰森:你想她以为什么,你把她的文章改的像地图,我的一个字都没改.
Jason: Well what did you she think she thought, you made marks on hers like a road map.Not even a comment on mine.
道格:我只是在看第二遍的时候批改.
Doug: I only make marks on my second pass.
我实在不想看第二遍.
I just couldn't face reading that again.
杰森:我的文章就没你喜欢的吗?
Jason: Well was there anything you liked about mine?
道格:呃…呃…呃…
Doug: Uhhh....Uhhh....Umm...
杰森:好吧.我懂了.
Jason: Ok, I get the picture.
麦琪:哦,杰森.
Maggie: Oh Jason.
杰森:我懂了.我懂了.没关系的.
Jason: I got it, I got it.That's no problem, it's fine.
我没事.这很好.家里再见吧.
That's ok , I'll see you at home.
麦琪:亲爱的.
Maggie: Honey.
杰森:呃,呃.
Jason: Uh huh.
麦琪:你还好吧?
Maggie: Are you alright?
杰森:哦,很好.
Jason: Oh yeah.
麦琪:你知道你走后,我想让道格把专栏收回,
Maggie: You know after you left,
我不写了.
part of me wanted to tell Doug to take his column and sit on it.
杰森:你不必这样的.
Jason: Well that wasn't necessary.
麦琪:幸运的是,我最后接受了那个专栏.
Maggie: Fortunately the part of me that spoke accepted the column.
但我正告他对你太无理了.
But I did tell hi I resented the way he treated you.
杰森:他是很粗鲁,是不是?但他是对的.
Jason: Well he was blunt, wasn't he, but he was right.
我看了你的文章,麦琪.没有模糊术语,
I got a copy of your article Maggie, no buzzwords, no passive sentences,
没有被动句.你的文字敏锐,
only sharp, intelligent, funny.
机智,有趣,让我想起了跟佛里德伊斯泰尔跳舞的那个晚上.
Reminded me of the night I danced with Fred Estair.
麦琪:你从没跟佛里德伊斯泰尔跳过舞.
Maggie: You never danced with Fred Estair.
杰森:不,我跳过.那晚我在看电视,
Jason: Yes I did.I was watching Top Hat on TV.
看见佛里德起身跳了几步,
Fred got up and did some of those steps, made it look easy.
看起来很简单.我也起来学着跳了几步,
I got up and did some of those steps,
还做出了一个高难的动作.
did a big kick and popped a hamstring.
从那时起,我就认识到只有真正的高手才能让困难看起来容易.
That's when I realized you have to be a real pro to make something so
麦琪,你就是这样的专家.
hard look so easy Maggie.And you are a pro.
麦琪:哦,杰森!你不觉得屋里有点热吗?
Maggie: Oh Jason!Don't you think it's a little warm in here?
杰森:我去开窗户.
Jason: I will open the window.
麦琪:哦,不是,不是那种热.
Maggie: No no, not that kind of warm puppy toes. Jason: Oh...
杰森:哦…是那种热.00:22:37,300
that kind of warm.